Anyway, I didn't steal you very much.
不管怎么说   我不怎么偷人
After all, you's only a little thing.
毕竟你们也太微小啦
I can't help thinking about
我一直在想
your poor mother and father, they must be...
你那可怜的爸爸妈妈一定
I don't have a mother or father.
我没有爸爸妈妈啦
You don't?
你没有吗
They both died when I was a baby.
我还是婴儿的时候   他们就过世啦
So you is an orphan?
所以你是个孤儿吗
Yes. You took me from an orphanage.
是的   你从孤儿院把我抓走的呀
You didn't know?
你之前不知道吗
I... I didn't know that.
我   确实没注意呢
Were you happy there?
你在那里过得快乐吗
No. I hate it.
不   我恨那个地方
The matron who runs it is incompetent and
管理孤儿院的妇女们 都很不称职
she has crazy rules and you get punished a lot.
制定很多疯狂的规定   而且还经常惩罚我
How is you punished?
她们怎么惩罚你呀
She locks you in a dark cellar. There are rats down there.
她把我关在黑黑的地窖里   里面还有老鼠呢
The filthy old fizzwiggler.
那些肮脏的臭家伙们
The other giants...
其他的巨人们
Are they nice, like you're nice?
他们和你一样   也很友好吗
No, I's sorry to say the boys would eat you up in one dollop.
很遗憾告诉你   他们会一口把你吃掉